

# Apostolos Gouvalas Full-stack Web Developer

Full-stack developer with over  $6.6 \chi p \acute{o} v i \alpha$  of experience in PHP, SQL and JavaScript, among other languages. With attention to detail and a passion for problem solving, I am willing to contribute my skills to dynamic and challenging projects.

■ apo.gouv@gmail.com

+30-697 8811 469

cubedesigns.gr

▼ Thessaloniki, Greece

### SOCIAL

in linkedin.com/in/apostolos-gouvalas

github.com/ApoGouv

#### **EDUCATION**

MS in Mobile and Web Computing

2016 - 2018

[ Distinction ]

International Hellenic University (Thessaloniki, Greece)

Digital Systems Degree, majoring in "Communication and Network Systems"

2004 - 2013

University of Piraeus - Department of Digital Systems (Piraeus, Athens, Greece)

#### **LANGUAGES**

Greek [Native language]
English [Proficiency of Michigan & IELTS 7.5]
Spanish [A2 in progress]

#### **SOFTWARE & TOOLS**

VSCode, Git, Linux, Windows, etc.

### **HOBBIES**

Cycling, Dancing Salsa/ Kizomba, Sudoku, Rock Music

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

## Full-stack Web Developer

Nov 2017 - Present | MultiHosting / Mental Media

- Development of Online Stores, with OpenCart, CS-Cart, PrestaShop, WooCommerce, etc., as well as custom functionalities and bridging with ERP.
- Website Development (portfolios, corporate, personal, etc.) - WordPress, Joomla, etc.
- Company Projects WHMCS, Laravel, vBulletin, Joomla, etc.

## Front-end Web Developer

Aug 2017 - Oct 2017 | PSDGator

 Convert design mockups from PSD or AI to valid HTML and CSS or WordPress Themes.

## Full-stack Web Developer

Dec 2015 - Present | Freelance

 Construction of websites, e-shops and custom solutions according to customer requirements

### Front-end Web Developer

Apr 2014 - May 2014 | igraphics.gr

 Creating the user interface based on the supplied graphic mockups, for applications to visualize the results for the 2014 Italian European Parliament Elections and display past Italian election results, with HTML, CSS and jQuery.

### **CERTIFICATES**

JavaScript, React, Node.js, PHP, κ.α.

2017 - 2024 | Udemy

Build a Social Network from Scratch: JavaScript PHP + MySQL Jan 01, 2019

The Complete Node.js Developer Course (2nd Edition) Oct 09, 2017

The Complete JavaScript Course:

Build a Real-World Project Sep 11, 2017

JavaScript Essentials Aug 14, 2017